[{"answer": "Hi, Sarah.  Come on in.  Im Carla, one of the International Student Advisors here", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hi Carla.  Nice to meet you", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Hi, Sarah.  Come on in.  Im Carla, one of the International Student Advisors here", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": "How can I help you today", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hi Carla.  Nice to meet you", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Well, Id like to travel home to see my family over the summer vacation and ", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 18, "question": "How can I help you today", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Sure.  Im glad you came in to check.  Are you traveling anywhere else beside", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Well, Id like to travel home to see my family over the summer vacation and ", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " No.  Im just going home and back", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Sure.  Im glad you came in to check.  Are you traveling anywhere else beside", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " OK.  How long will you be gone", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 27, "question": " No.  Im just going home and back", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Ill be there for 4 weeks", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 28, "question": " OK.  How long will you be gone", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " OK.  That sounds fine.   In order to travel you have to bring with you your vali", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Ill be there for 4 weeks", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " What do you mean by signed I-20", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 37, "question": " OK.  That sounds fine.   In order to travel you have to bring with you your vali", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Well, if you want to travel out of the US you need to get a travel signature on pag", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 38, "question": " What do you mean by signed I-20", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Who signs it", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Well, if you want to travel out of the US you need to get a travel signature on pag", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": "I do.  Or another International Student Advisor.  Ill take your I-20 today and i", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Who signs it", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Cant you sign it right now", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 47, "question": "I do.  Or another International Student Advisor.  Ill take your I-20 today and i", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " No.  We have to pull your file and check your status, which takes a little while", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Cant you sign it right now", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Oh, OK.  I had a question about my F-1 visa too.  Its going to expire the da", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 49, "question": " No.  We have to pull your file and check your status, which takes a little while", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " No, it shouldnt.  You can use your visa for re-entry into the U.S. up until midnigh", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Oh, OK.  I had a question about my F-1 visa too.  Its going to expire the da", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Oh, good!  I was hoping that I wouldnt have to make a trip to the embassy whil", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 57, "question": " No, it shouldnt.  You can use your visa for re-entry into the U.S. up until midnigh", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Yeah.  Its a hassle for a lot of students", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Oh, good!  I was hoping that I wouldnt have to make a trip to the embassy whil", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Oh, another thing.  What about my I-94 card? How does that work?  Do I alway", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Yeah.  Its a hassle for a lot of students", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " No, the I-94 card is what the government uses to track your entries into an", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Oh, another thing.  What about my I-94 card? How does that work?  Do I alway", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 70, "question": " No, the I-94 card is what the government uses to track your entries into an", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Yep.  So at the airport when you leave the agents should take your I-94 card.  O", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Is that the same process for all countries", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Yep.  So at the airport when you leave the agents should take your I-94 card.  O", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " It is.  Except for Canada and Mexico.  If you travel there its different, but we ca", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Is that the same process for all countries", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 83, "question": " It is.  Except for Canada and Mexico.  If you travel there its different, but we ca", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " So, just make sure all your documents are valid and well sign your I-20 and yo", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 84, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " No, I dont think so.  You answered everything", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 88, "question": " So, just make sure all your documents are valid and well sign your I-20 and yo", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Good", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 89, "question": " No, I dont think so.  You answered everything", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Thanks for your help", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Good", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Come back anytime you have a question", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Thanks for your help", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " I will", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Youre welcome.  Come back anytime you have a question", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": "Bye!  Have a great trip", "docId": "05-04", "aSentId": 93, "question": " I will", "qSentId": 92}]
